<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:foaf="http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/" xmlns:og="http://ogp.me/ns#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:schema="http://schema.org/" xmlns:sioc="http://rdfs.org/sioc/ns#" xmlns:sioct="http://rdfs.org/sioc/types#" xmlns:skos="http://www.w3.org/2004/02/skos/core#" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#" version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.us-cert.gov/">
  <channel>
    <title>CISA ICS Alerts</title>
    <link>https://www.us-cert.gov/</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    
    <item>
	<title>SweynTooth Vulnerabilities</title>
	<link>https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/alerts/ics-alert-20-063-01</link>
	<description>This ALERT details vulnerabilities in SweynTooth&amp;#039;s Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE) proof-of-concept (PoC) exploit code. This report was released without coordination with some of the affected vendors and without advance coordination with CISA. CISA has notified some of the affected vendors of the report and has asked the vendors to confirm the vulnerabilities and identify mitigations. </description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 10:20:19 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>ICS-CERT Alert Document</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/13760</guid>
    </item>
<item>
	<title>Mitsubishi Electric Europe B.V. smartRTU and INEA ME-RTU (Update A)</title>
	<link>https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/alerts/ics-alert-19-225-01</link>
	<description>This updated alert is a follow-up to the original alert titled ICS-ALERT-19-225-01 Mitsubishi Electric smartRTU and INEA ME-RTU that was published August 13, 2019, on the ICS webpage on us-cert.gov. CISA is aware of a public report of a proof-of-concept (PoC) exploit code vulnerability affecting Mitsubishi Electric smartRTU devices. According to this report, there are multiple vulnerabilities that could result in remote code execution with root privileges. CISA is issuing this alert to provide early notice of the report.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 10:30:44 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>ICS-CERT Alert Document</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/12713</guid>
    </item>
<item>
	<title>CAN Bus Network Implementation in Avionics</title>
	<link>https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/alerts/ics-alert-19-211-01</link>
	<description>CISA is aware of a public report of insecure implementation of CAN bus networks affecting aircraft. According to this report, the CAN bus networks are exploitable when an attacker has unsupervised physical access to the aircraft. CISA is issuing this alert to provide early notice of the report.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 09:00:02 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>ICS-CERT Alert Document</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/12641</guid>
    </item>
<item>
	<title>DICOM Standard in Medical Devices</title>
	<link>https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/alerts/ICS-ALERT-19-162-01</link>
	<description>NCCIC is aware of a public report of a vulnerability in the DICOM (Digital Imaging and Communications in Medicine) standard with proof-of-concept (PoC) exploit code. The DICOM standard is the international standard to transmit, store, retrieve, print, process, and display medical imaging information. According to this report, the vulnerability is exploitable by embedding executable code into the 128 byte preamble. This report was released without coordination with NCCIC or any known vendor.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 12:15:03 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>ICS-CERT Alert Document</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/12412</guid>
    </item>
<item>
	<title>Meltdown and Spectre Vulnerabilities (Update J)</title>
	<link>https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/alerts/ICS-ALERT-18-011-01</link>
	<description>This updated alert is a follow-up to the updated alert titled ICS-ALERT-18-011-01 Meltdown and Spectre Vulnerabilities (Update I) that was published September 11, 2018, on the NCCIC/ICS-CERT website.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 12:51:19 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>ICS-CERT Alert Document</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/11850</guid>
    </item>
<item>
	<title>WAGO PFC200</title>
	<link>https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/alerts/ICS-ALERT-17-341-01</link>
	<description>NCCIC is aware of a public report of an improper authentication vulnerability affecting WAGO PFC200, a Programmable Logic Controller (PLC) device. According to this report, the vulnerability is exploitable by sending a TCP payload on the bound port. This report was released after attempted coordination with WAGO. NCCIC has notified the affected vendor of the report and has asked the vendor to confirm the vulnerability and identify mitigations. NCCIC is issuing this alert to provide notice of the report and identify baseline mitigations for reducing risks to these and other cybersecurity attacks.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 16:11:13 EST</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>ICS-CERT Alert Document</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/11849</guid>
    </item>
<item>
	<title>Eaton ELCSoft Vulnerabilities</title>
	<link>https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/alerts/ICS-ALERT-17-216-01-0</link>
	<description>NCCIC/ICS-CERT is aware of a public report of buffer overflow vulnerabilities affecting Eaton ELCSoft, a PLC programming software for Eaton Logic Control (ELC) controllers. According to the public report, which was coordinated with ICS-CERT prior to its public release, researcher Ariele Caltabiano (kimiya) working with Trend Micro&amp;amp;#039;s Zero Day Initiative, identified that an attacker can leverage these vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the process. ICS-CERT has notified the affected vendor, who has reported that they are planning to address the vulnerabilities. No timeline has been provided. ICS-CERT is issuing this alert to provide notice of the report and to identify baseline mitigations for reducing risks to these and other cybersecurity attacks.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 15:11:04 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>ICS-CERT Alert Document</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/11848</guid>
    </item>
<item>
	<title>CAN Bus Standard Vulnerability</title>
	<link>https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/alerts/ICS-ALERT-17-209-01</link>
	<description>NCCIC/ICS-CERT is aware of a public report of a vulnerability in the Controller Area Network (CAN) Bus standard with proof-of-concept (PoC) exploit code affecting CAN Bus, a broadcast based network standard. According to the public report, which was coordinated with ICS-CERT prior to its public release, researchers Andrea Palanca, Eric Evenchick, Federico Maggi, and Stefano Zanero identified a vulnerability exploiting a weakness in the CAN protocol that allows an attacker to perform a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:34:04 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>ICS-CERT Alert Document</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/11847</guid>
    </item>
<item>
	<title>CRASHOVERRIDE Malware</title>
	<link>https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/alerts/ICS-ALERT-17-206-01</link>
	<description>CRASHOVERRIDE, aka, Industroyer, is the fourth family of malware publically identified as targeting industrial control systems (ICS). It uses a modular design, with payloads that target several industrial communication protocols and are capable of directly controlling switches and circuit breakers. Additional modules include a data-wiping component and a module capable of causing a denial of service (DoS) to Siemens SIPROTEC devices.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 12:45:14 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>ICS-CERT Alert Document</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/11846</guid>
    </item>
<item>
	<title>Petya Malware Variant (Update C)</title>
	<link>https://www.us-cert.gov/ics/alerts/ICS-ALERT-17-181-01C</link>
	<description>This updated alert is a follow-up to the updated alert titled ICS-ALERT-17-181-01B Petya Malware Variant that was published July 5, 2017, on the NCCIC/ICS-CERT web site. ICS-CERT is aware of reports of a variant of the Petya malware that is affecting several countries. ICS-CERT is releasing this alert to enhance the awareness of critical infrastructure asset owners/operators about the Petya variant and to identify product vendors that have issued recommendations to mitigate the risk associated with this malware.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 17:09:05 EDT</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>ICS-CERT Alert Document</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">/node/11845</guid>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
